<xml>
    <news>
        <date>09.01.2019</date>
        <time>09:39</time>
        <title>In St. Petersburg will begin to distribute the first ribbons " Leningrad victory"</title>
        <shortDescription>On January 9, the campaign "Ribbon of the Leningrad Victory"will be launched in the Northern capital.</shortDescription>
        <fullDescription>On January 9, the campaign "Ribbon of the Leningrad Victory"will be launched in the Northern capital. On this day, the city will host several celebrations, which will begin to hand over the first ribbons. Meetings of veterans of the blockade will be held at 15.00 at the Leningrad plant of bread named after S. M. Kirov, at 16.30 in the bookshop of writers, at 18.00 at the St. Petersburg theater Russian enterprise named after Andrei Mironov.
            
            All volunteers present will be handed blockade ribbons, which is a strip of fabric of two colors: olive and green. The olive color of the ribbon symbolizes Victory, and green — the color of life. They also repeat the colors of the medal "for the defense of Leningrad" — the main award of the blockade.
            
            Earlier it was reported that in honor of the 75th anniversary of the lifting of the siege of Leningrad blockade veterans will receive special cash payments, and in the bunker of Smolny will open a Museum about the blockade.</fullDescription>
        <source>Source: https://peterburg2.ru</source>
        <croppedPicture>https://peterburg2.ru/uploads/19/01/09/s10_546864868481.jpg</croppedPicture>
        <picture>https://peterburg2.ru/uploads/19/01/09/s10_546864868481.jpg</picture>
    </news>
    <news>
        <date>08.01.2019</date>
        <time>23:12</time>
        <title>The details of the naval parade in 2019 are disclosed</title>
        <shortDescription>The main naval parade, which was first held in St. Petersburg in 2017, became an annual event. The other day, the Navy commander-in-Chief revealed the details of what awaits the spectators of the parade in July 2019.</shortDescription>
        <fullDescription>The main naval parade, which was first held in St. Petersburg in 2017, became an annual event. The other day, the Navy commander-in-Chief revealed the details of what awaits the spectators of the parade in July 2019. The commander-in-chief of the Navy of the Russian Federation Admiral Vladimir Korolev said that work has already begun to improve the preparation and conduct of the parade on the Neva river and the Kronstadt RAID.
            
            In July 2019, it is planned to present new ships, equipment, as well as new spectacular episodes, which are not yet disclosed and kept secret, will be prepared. It was also about a possible increase in the composition of the forces participating in the parade.
            
            Recall that in 2018 in the parade, held in St. Petersburg and Kronstadt, participated 41 surface ship and submarine and 38 aircraft.</fullDescription>
        <source>Source: https://peterburg2.ru</source>
        <croppedPicture>https://peterburg2.ru/uploads/19/01/08/o_1bO6aU0XVTE.jpg</croppedPicture>
        <picture>https://peterburg2.ru/uploads/19/01/08/s10_1bO6aU0XVTE_0.jpg</picture>
    </news>
    <news>
        <date>08.01.2019</date>
        <time>22:11</time>
        <title>In the Leningrad region at the rink found wintering hedgehog</title>
        <shortDescription>In the Pine forest during the pouring town's ice skating rink randomly found wintered at the site of hedgehog.</shortDescription>
        <fullDescription>In the Pine forest during the pouring town's ice skating rink randomly found wintered at the site of hedgehog. Sosnovoborsky pulled discovered at the rink hedgehog, so that when the fill was not hurt, not cold and was not under the ice.
            
            The author of the video Alex Bencler in the comments to the post said that the animal is now sleeping in the basement on a box in a man-made "hole".
            
            Hedgehog, according to eyewitnesses, during the rescue operation never woke up, just a loud snoring.</fullDescription>
        <source>Source: https://peterburg2.ru</source>
        <croppedPicture>https://peterburg2.ru/uploads/19/01/08/o_118397797_original__73__0.jpg</croppedPicture>
        <picture></picture>
    </news>
    <news>
        <date>08.01.2019</date>
        <time>20:26</time>
        <title>How was the festival of fire And light in St. Petersburg</title>
        <shortDescription>7 and 8 January in St. Petersburg hosted the festival of fire and light "Christmas star".</shortDescription>
        <fullDescription>7 and 8 January in St. Petersburg hosted the festival of fire and light "Christmas star". The facade of the Exchange building on the spit of Vasilievsky island for two evenings turned into a canvas on which various 3D projections appeared. The festival program also included fireworks, fire and light performances. As it was - in our special collection of social networks.</fullDescription>
        <source>Source: https://peterburg2.ru</source>
        <croppedPicture>https://peterburg2.ru/uploads/19/01/08/s10_49294546_511210839373501_3096282857830459729_n.jpg</croppedPicture>
        <picture></picture>
    </news>
    <news>
        <date>03.01.2019</date>
        <time>23:17</time>
        <title>Comedy about the siege of Leningrad officially published on Youtube</title>
        <shortDescription>The film is called "Holiday", and its plot unfolds in the besieged Leningrad on New year's eve. The motion picture appeared in theaters and in open access on YouTube-the channel of the Director of the film Alexey Krasovsky.</shortDescription>
        <fullDescription>The film is called "Holiday", and its plot unfolds in the besieged Leningrad on New year's eve. The motion picture appeared in theaters and in open access on YouTube-the channel of the Director of the film Alexey Krasovsky. January 3 on the Youtube channel of the film Director Alexei Krasovsky published a scandalous Comedy about the siege of Leningrad.
            
            It is noted that although the film was posted for free, but the team will be able to transfer money to the details specified under the video. Recall the film, shot in seven days, criticized for his blasphemy and demanded not to show in theaters. The film was played by Alena Babenko, Jan Tsapnik, Pavel Tabakov, and the Director of photography was Sergei Astakhov, known from the films of Alexei Balabanov.
            
            At the time of publication of the news, according to the statistics of Youtube-service, the film was liked by 9.4 thousand viewers, did not like - 5.7 thousand among the comments to the film there are more positive reviews.</fullDescription>
        <source>Source: https://peterburg2.ru</source>
        <croppedPicture>https://peterburg2.ru/uploads/19/01/03/o_63ab165fb2c767666c41ad288916b1a6-1440x_0.png</croppedPicture>
        <picture></picture>
    </news>
    <news>
        <date>03.01.2019</date>
        <time>20:35</time>
        <title>The Hermitage changed the day of free admission</title>
        <shortDescription>Once a month, huge queues line up in the Hermitage across the entire Palace square to get into the most famous repository of valuables. However, now the date of free entry has changed.</shortDescription>
        <fullDescription>Once a month, huge queues line up in the Hermitage across the entire Palace square to get into the most famous repository of valuables. However, now the date of free entry has changed. Previously, free access to the Hermitage was possible on the first Thursday of the month, may 18 and December 7.
            
            However, on January 3, 2019, many visitors, after standing in a huge queue, found that now in the Hermitage the third Thursday of each month became a preferential day of visit.
            
            Petersburgers and guests complained on social networks that there were no news on changing the dates with free entrance.
            
            On the website of the Hermitage, information that the third Thursday of each month is the day of free access to the Museum for all categories of individual visitors (with free tickets) can be found only in the "Tickets"section.
            
            Peterburg2.ru found in the VK group of Museum communication, dated 26 December, on entry c 1.01.2019 the new changes for free visit.</fullDescription>
        <source>Source: https://peterburg2.ru</source>
        <croppedPicture>https://peterburg2.ru/uploads/19/01/03/o_%D0%A1%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%BC%D0%BE%D0%BA_0.jpg</croppedPicture>
        <picture></picture>
    </news>
</xml>
